<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Top Archives - Unpaused (by Keya)</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/top/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/category/top/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 09:38:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Screenshot-2023-07-16-at-3.31.43-PM-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Top Archives - Unpaused (by Keya)</title>
	<link>/category/top/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>home</title>
		<link>/home/</link>
					<comments>/home/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Keya Editor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 10:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Top]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://squatmissile.com/?p=436</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>home is a safety netexcept mine was a net,literally.ivory black brass poles decorated with a wedding-like veil                                           its hexagons teaching me life from different perspectives when i felt like i had no one those hexagons [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/home/">&lt;strong&gt;home&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Unpaused (by Keya)</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="wp-post" data-elementor-id="436" class="elementor elementor-436">
									<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-2565ed82 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default wpr-particle-no wpr-jarallax-no wpr-parallax-no wpr-sticky-section-no" data-id="2565ed82" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-7c524c75" data-id="7c524c75" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-19e4d3ac elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-id="19e4d3ac" data-element_type="widget" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInLeft&quot;}" data-widget_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<style>/*! elementor - v3.14.0 - 18-06-2023 */
.elementor-widget-text-editor.elementor-drop-cap-view-stacked .elementor-drop-cap{background-color:#69727d;color:#fff}.elementor-widget-text-editor.elementor-drop-cap-view-framed .elementor-drop-cap{color:#69727d;border:3px solid;background-color:transparent}.elementor-widget-text-editor:not(.elementor-drop-cap-view-default) .elementor-drop-cap{margin-top:8px}.elementor-widget-text-editor:not(.elementor-drop-cap-view-default) .elementor-drop-cap-letter{width:1em;height:1em}.elementor-widget-text-editor .elementor-drop-cap{float:left;text-align:center;line-height:1;font-size:50px}.elementor-widget-text-editor .elementor-drop-cap-letter{display:inline-block}</style>				<p></p>
<p>home is a safety net<br />except mine was a net,<br />literally.<br />ivory black brass poles decorated with a wedding-like veil                                         <span style="font-size: var(--wp--preset--font-size--medium); background-color: var(--wp--preset--color--background);">  its hexagons teaching me life from different perspectives when i felt like i had no one</span></p>
<p></p>
<p>those hexagons made me feel like home<br />a place to fall back on<br />for others they were just two metal poles<br />but those stumps were my pillars of support<br />the ones that held my world together every time it came crashing down shielding and protecting me from all the broken pieces.</p>
<p></p>
<p>if anyone,<br />those poles have seen my multitudes of failures<br />witnessed me drag through the tougher days<br />and feel the happiest on the better ones<br />yet those poles remain unmoved<br />rather involuntarily<br />but i’d like to think otherwise.<br />those 24&#215;8 feet have seen my life unfurl before them<br />as if they heard all the thoughts and sounds in my head<br />and assuaged themselves on the days i needed them to<br />letting some of my kicks roll in,<br />bringing me heaving sighs of relief<br />with chills running down my spine after hearing the swish of the ball against the net.<br />i like to think of the goal as my best friend<br />and however absurd it may sound<br />i hope that that 40 feet of black never fails to deliver me the solace that it does when i need it when i need someplace to feel nothing but safe<br />nothing but like home</p>
<p></p>						</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-5765986 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default wpr-particle-no wpr-jarallax-no wpr-parallax-no wpr-sticky-section-no" data-id="5765986" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-fd3affb" data-id="fd3affb" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-217e89e elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-id="217e89e" data-element_type="widget" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInUp&quot;}" data-widget_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<style>/*! elementor - v3.14.0 - 18-06-2023 */
.elementor-widget-image{text-align:center}.elementor-widget-image a{display:inline-block}.elementor-widget-image a img[src$=".svg"]{width:48px}.elementor-widget-image img{vertical-align:middle;display:inline-block}</style>												<img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1024" height="1007" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/IMG_1652-1024x1007.jpg" class="attachment-large size-large wp-image-438" alt="" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/IMG_1652-1024x1007.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/05/IMG_1652-300x295.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/05/IMG_1652-768x755.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/05/IMG_1652.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />															</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
							</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/home/">&lt;strong&gt;home&lt;/strong&gt;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Unpaused (by Keya)</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/home/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>a letter to future me</title>
		<link>/a-letter-to-future-me/</link>
					<comments>/a-letter-to-future-me/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Keya Editor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 09:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Top]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://squatmissile.com/?p=411</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Remember when all you ever wanted was all that you have today?It was all that you had ever envisioned for yourself.Like a canvas slathered with paints of all hues of emotions, in a room full of critically acclaimed artwork you would’ve still chosen that canvas,the one that was recklessly slapped with shades of the rainbow.You [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-letter-to-future-me/">a letter to future me</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Unpaused (by Keya)</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="wp-post" data-elementor-id="411" class="elementor elementor-411">
									<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-42320a76 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default wpr-particle-no wpr-jarallax-no wpr-parallax-no wpr-sticky-section-no" data-id="42320a76" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-3c0ea931" data-id="3c0ea931" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-16e1e211 elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-id="16e1e211" data-element_type="widget" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInLeft&quot;}" data-widget_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
							<p></p>
<p>Remember when all you ever wanted was all that you have today?<br>It was all that you had ever envisioned for yourself.<br>Like a canvas slathered with paints of all hues of emotions, in a room full of critically acclaimed artwork you would’ve still chosen that canvas,<br>the one that was recklessly slapped with shades of the rainbow.<br>You loved all of its cheeky yellows and bright blues in all their entirety.<br>You had promised to always choose the road not taken.<br>Do you break promises now?<br>A ‘pinky promise’ was the only thing you treasured more than Riyaaz-the doll you had pledged you would marry in kindergarten.<br>The neons didnt make you squint back then,<br>you didn’t hide away and shelter yourself from them, running away the way you do from most things anymore.<br>I hope you find solace in the monotones of grey you now call your home.<br>I hope you never realise how lonely a grey can make you feel.<br>The same palette, just different versions of the artist.<br>You’ve scraped all remnants of colour from your canvas,yet the hollowing pinks and purple will always remember the agony you felt when you first saw the shiny metal insides of their tin squares sparkle.<br>The blacks that you now find comfort in, they’re proof that people hold within them, the power of change. You only see red on the heavily cluttered makeup table now.<br>Yellow,at the break of dawn on your morning run.<br>Blue,in the needle of your weighing scale that you now use to quantify your worth as a human being. Greens,on the dinner table in great volumes of ‘healthy’.<br>Yet its only the white you resort to in the end,<br>the whites of the toilet bowl you press your arms on after meal, flushing with all the ‘nourishing’ greens, the guilt and anxiety.<br>All gone,<br>in a second’s worth of time.<br>Drained along with your self worth.<br>You suddenly feel something trickle down your cheek,<br>if ‘feel’ is even the right sensory term for it.<br>It tastes salty, like the water in Greece you had played in with your father when you were four,<br>they dont taste like ‘fun’ anymore.<br>Too numb to even wipe this taste off your cheek,<br>You sit there in the blacks and greys and the whites of the night,<br>feeling like the hollowed purples and pinks of your watercolour box.<br>Yet theres no amalgamation of colour, thats felt like this.<br>But, I hope you find one soon, soon enough to paint your canvas with before you choose to discard it.&nbsp;</p><p>Soon enough to remember that you were once,<br>a mixture of purples, now blacks and next,<br>whatever you choose to be.</p>
<p></p>						</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-c37df2c elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default wpr-particle-no wpr-jarallax-no wpr-parallax-no wpr-sticky-section-no" data-id="c37df2c" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-3578896" data-id="3578896" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-812fec1 elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-id="812fec1" data-element_type="widget" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInUp&quot;}" data-widget_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
															<img decoding="async" width="748" height="750" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-19-at-3.15.24-PM.png" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large wp-image-413" alt="" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-19-at-3.15.24-PM.png 748w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-19-at-3.15.24-PM-300x300.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Screenshot-2023-05-19-at-3.15.24-PM-150x150.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 748px) 100vw, 748px" />															</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
							</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-letter-to-future-me/">a letter to future me</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Unpaused (by Keya)</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/a-letter-to-future-me/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>the fourth pillar of democracy.</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-pillar-of-democracy/</link>
					<comments>/the-fourth-pillar-of-democracy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Keya Editor]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 06:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Top]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://squatmissile.com/?p=324</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today,any sixth grade student who has barely paid any attention in civics class will know what the three pillars of democracy are. Yet,it’s always the fourth pillar that remains unknown and uncontested. For those of you who skipped out on some civics lessons, the fourth pillar of democracy is the press. The press is so [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-pillar-of-democracy/">the fourth pillar of democracy.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Unpaused (by Keya)</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="wp-post" data-elementor-id="324" class="elementor elementor-324">
									<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-b6a2aae elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default wpr-particle-no wpr-jarallax-no wpr-parallax-no wpr-sticky-section-no" data-id="b6a2aae" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-712e8a52" data-id="712e8a52" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-15859b76 elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-id="15859b76" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
							
<p>Today,any sixth grade student who has barely paid any attention in civics class will know what the three pillars of democracy are. Yet,it’s always the fourth pillar that remains unknown and uncontested. For those of you who skipped out on some civics lessons, the fourth pillar of democracy is the press.</p>

<p>The press is so ubiquitous in the 21st century that we often forget how important it is. The freedom of press is the freedom of being able to fearlessly hold an opinion, to have a thought and to be able to boldly call it yours. With India celebrating its 75 years of independence, we don’t just celebrate those who fought with their swords but also those who fought with their pens. The press is a timeless entity and its importance was highlighted a 100 years ago, in 1922 when Bapu was prisoned on charges of sedition, its being highlighted now with Kashmiri journalists still being cuffed with every idea they pen and will still remain of utmost importance when 20 years from now someone from this room will be using the same freedom to make a change in society. In a country like India,it is the vernacular press that made us reach where we are today. It was the string that stitched us together in the tapestry of the tricolor we proudly call ours.</p>

<p>The freedom of establishing your opinion also carries with it the brunt of responsibility. The power of being able to construct and deconstruct nations altogether. When the freedom of press is curtailed,the true essence of democracy crumbles to dust. In this dust lie the ashes of those like Gauri Lankesh and Danish Siddiqui but with them the plethora of names that we conveniently overlook at the end of our daily morning newspapers.</p>

<p>This liberty isn’t only limited to those sitting in a Reuters office or a politicians Bureau,it is equally applicable to everyone who wants to know what happened in the Capitol Riots or just simply understand whether religion is actually about beliefs or just political propaganda.It is applicable to children who want to know who won the Cricket match this evening and also those who just want to post a comment in support of Mahsa Amini on their Instagram profiles.The freedom of press concerns the one family in Syria whose only way out is through substantial change as much as it does the one reporter who wants to publish this as his last article because he will be facing harsh consequences to his actions.</p>

<p>The world names the ones who had to work tirelessly in hospitals in the wake of the pandemic as its frontline heroes. What about those who stood outside reporting these dire circumstances to you,ones who stood there unwaveringly firm so that you could have a glimpse of what was uncovering behind the N-95 masks and the oxygen cylinders from the comfort of your 75 inch TVs. A Dmitry Muratov or a Maria Ressa would have never been able to reach the surface if their liberty to efficiently report and deliver would have been scrapped off.</p>

<p>“Where the mind is without fear and the head is held high”</p>

<p>These lines were written by Tagore to explain to our country how glorious an independent nation would have felt. If it weren’t for the freedom of press these lines would have been a paradox in itself. The press gives people substance to build their opinion on,without substance what are humans if not empty vessels with decorative sheaths on themselves. Today I know what and what not to fear because my ‘Hindu’ subscription gives me the liberty to decide it.</p>

<p>When I was told to write this essay today, I was asked to explain the degree of importance that the press holds. My sheer incapability of writing this article if it weren’t for the freedom that was given to me to write it and to the ones that conveyed their ideas to me through square shaped columns and miniscule blog articles are proof enough that freedom of press holds the utmost important today,and always will even centuries from now.</p>

<p>This essay isn’t about students studying journalism in Yale or aspiring writers who want to make in the field it is about that girl who didnt have the privilege of missing her civics class because her education was blatantly scrapped off her schedule,on the lines of war and terrorism. She knows best what the fourth pillar of democracy is because it is the same pillar that came crashing down when she read of her brother’s name in the list of those martyred in the morning paper the day Kashmir was captured.</p>

<p>The press has successfully saved humanity in times of peril and those of comfort alike. As the fonts under every article progressively shrinks,it is our duty to make sure that their liberties as individuals don’t. it is our duty that we save today what has always saved us,to give back to the one construct that has never failed the ‘for the people’ part of democracy.</p>
						</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-c754d0b elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default wpr-particle-no wpr-jarallax-no wpr-parallax-no wpr-sticky-section-no" data-id="c754d0b" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-e32a3f7" data-id="e32a3f7" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-3a502a2 elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-id="3a502a2" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
															<img decoding="async" width="800" height="521" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/6a014e5f5d3c7c970c01bb09971faa970d.jpg" class="attachment-large size-large wp-image-325" alt="" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/6a014e5f5d3c7c970c01bb09971faa970d.jpg 800w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/05/6a014e5f5d3c7c970c01bb09971faa970d-300x195.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/05/6a014e5f5d3c7c970c01bb09971faa970d-768x500.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" />															</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
							</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-pillar-of-democracy/">the fourth pillar of democracy.</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Unpaused (by Keya)</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/the-fourth-pillar-of-democracy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
